http://www.satplus.com.au/pages/privacy-policy

VIEW OUR CHRISTMAS SPECIALS ON ROOF MOUNTED SATELLITE SYSTEMS, LITHIUM BATTERIES, VAST DECODERS WITH SHELF BRACKETS & MORE!
Roof Mounted & Automatic Satellite Systems
Portable RV Dishes Only (Not Full Kits)
Mobile Internet
Maxview Roam Mobile 3G/4G Wifi Caravan Motorhome Internet System
TWIN Cigarette Splitter
Altech 4921 Acessories Pack (12V Lead, IR Sensor)
Shopping Cart
Your cart is currently empty.
Continue Shopping
My Account
Welcome to SatPlus Australia!
Privacy Policy
Satplus' Commitment to Online Security & Information Security
Your personal information is treated with the greatest of care. Sensitive payment information such as credit card details are NEVER stored on the Internet or on any Satplus computer or database. Once you type your information, it is sent instantly, encrypted, directly to our order processing system. We employ the latest 1024-bit encryption technology in all areas of the site which require you to provide payment information. This is done to protect you from unauthorized use of the information you are sending to our server. The Website is registered with site identification authorities to enable your browser to confirm our security identity before any transmission is sent. With this technology, the identity of this site is automatically confirmed behind the scenes prior to the transmission of any sensitive information requested to complete an online order and ensures that your data reaches your intended target or your browser notifies you that the potential receiving site looks suspicious and should be avoided.
Card details obtained from telephone transactions are never held after authorization and are destroyed at the end of each working day.
Our aim is to comply at all times with the privacy laws (incorporating the Australian Privacy Principles) that apply to us. If you have a comment, query or complaint regarding a privacy matter, we encourage you to discuss it with us. “Contact us link”
What personal information Satplus collects and how it is managed:
We may collect the following types of personal information from you:
name
address
phone number
email address
information about the goods you have ordered
information from enquiries you have made
communications between us
Any of the above information we collect may be used in one of the following ways:
To process transactions
To maintain a transaction history
Responding to customer enquiries
Should you choose to create an account on www.satplus.com.au the above information may be used to create a database for the provision of subscription to a bi-monthly newsletter. You can unsubscribe from this service at any time by emailing enquiries@satplus.com.au
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product (eg Australia Post) or service requested, or in exceptional circumstances, to law enforcement and national security agencies, and other government and regulatory authorities as required or authorised by law.
Your personal information is stored within secure systems that are protected in controlled facilities. Staff are obliged to respect the confidentiality of any personal information held by us.
Cookies
We use cookies on our websites. Cookies can make using our websites easier by storing information about your preferences and enabling you to take full advantage of our services. Cookies are very small text files that a website can transfer to your computer’s hard drive for record keeping.
We may also use cookies so that we can determine which parts of our websites are visited most often, or whether you visited our site from a banner advertisement for one of our products and services on another party’s website.
Most internet web browsers are pre-set to accept cookies to enable full use of websites that employ them. However, if you do not wish to receive any cookies you may configure your browser to reject them or receive a warning when cookies are being used. In some instances, this may mean that you will not be able to use some or all of the services provided on our website. However you may still be able to access information-only pages.
Social media
Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button and Widgets, such as the Share This button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are hosted by a third party. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.
Complaints
If you have concerns or wish to make a complaint regarding the handling of your personal information by us please contact us.   “contact us link”
Changes
If we make changes to our privacy policy, we will post those on the website prior to the change becoming effective so that you are aware of any alteration in what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.
We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time. These amendments will take effect from the time of posting and we remind and encourage you to check back from time to time for any changes.
This policy was last modified on 15/8/2014.
Main Menu
Home
Browse Products
Information
Demo & Help Videos
Contact Us
TRADE LOGIN
Privacy and Returns
Privacy Policy
Returns Policy
Keep in Touch
Sign up to our newsletter and receive up to date information on our latest products relating to the world of satellite TV
© 2020 SatPlus Australia
|
x
Net Orders Checkout
Item
Price
Qty
Total
Mozambique
Myanmar (Burma)
Namibia
Nauru
Nepal
Netherlands
Netherlands Antilles
New Caledonia
New Zealand
Nicaragua
Zimbabwe
AlabamaAlaskaAmerican SamoaArizonaArkansasCaliforniaColoradoConnecticutDelawareDistrict of ColumbiaFederated States of MicronesiaFloridaGeorgiaGuamHawaiiIdahoIllinoisIndianaIowaKansasKentuckyLouisianaMaineMarshall IslandsMarylandMassachusettsMichiganMinnesotaMississippiMissouriMontanaNebraskaNevadaNew HampshireNew JerseyNew MexicoNew YorkNorth CarolinaNorth DakotaNorthern Mariana IslandsOhioOklahomaOregonPalauPennsylvaniaPuerto RicoRhode IslandSouth CarolinaSouth DakotaTennesseeTexasUtahVermontVirgin IslandsVirginiaWashingtonWest VirginiaWisconsinWyomingArmed Forces AmericasArmed Forces EuropeArmed Forces Pacific
Shipping Methods
